Guide to the Big Band Arrangements Collection, 1990-2017 SC.2017.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Big Band Arrangements Collection
1990-2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Greco, Raymond J. (James)
SC.2017.01
63.75 Linear Feet
The collection documents the arranging and performance career of Raymond J. (James) Greco (1921-2003), bandleader of the Ray Vincent Orchestra. His band was dedicated to recreating the Glenn Miller sound, and the arrangements reflect his skill in adapting standard tunes to this style.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in seven series, each focusing on different types of ensembles: Big Band, Nine-Man, Tenor, Four Horn, Ten to Twelve Man, Two-Way, and Three-Way. Instrumental parts are included for each piece, and if a vocal part is included, that is indicated in the finding aid.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Raymond Greco, Jr. on June 23, 2017.
Biography
Raymond J. Greco (1921–2003) was the founder and leader of the Ray Vincent Orchestra. Born in Peterstown, West Virginia, Greco was private first class in the U.S. Army during World War II. As a music figure, Greco was the arranger of big band standards for the Orchestra. Dedicated to recreating the Glenn Miller Sound, the Ray Vincent Orchestra performed widely in the southwest Pennsylvania area, as well as in West Virginia. Greco passed away in Weston, Florida, in 2003.
Scope and Content Notes
The collection documents the arranging and performance career of Raymond J. (James) Greco (1921-2003), bandleader of the Ray Vincent Orchestra. His band was dedicated to recreating the Glenn Miller sound, and the arrangements reflect his skill in adapting standard tunes to this style.
Arrangement (Music); Jazz; Big Band Music -- Parts; Ray Vincent Orchestra; Greco, Raymond J. (James)
- Big Band Arrangements, I.
  - 23-N 82 W (Stan Kenton) (Box 17, Folder 1094)
  - 720 In the Books (Jan Savit) (Box 4, Folder 232)
  - 920 Special (Harry James) (Box 4, Folder 239)
  - 920 Special (Box 23, Folder 2272)
  - A Ballad (Oliver Nelson) (Box 18, Folder 1105)
  - A Fine Romance (Ted Heath) (Box 27, Folder 2492)
  - A Foggy Day, Vocal (Bb) (Box 8, Folder 464)
  - A Foggy Day (Ray Anthony) (Box 24, Folder 2344)
  - A Good Man is Hard to Find, Vocal (C) (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - A Hundred Years, Vocal (Bb) (Box 13, Folder 777)
  - A Little Minor Booze (Stan Kenton) (Box 18, Folder 1099)
  - A Lovely Way to Spend an Evening, Vocal Group (Bb) (Box 19, Folder 1189)
  - A Lovely Way to Spend an Evening (The Four Freshmen), Vocal Group (Box 10, Folder 634)
  - A Man with a Horn (Ray Anthony) (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - A Man Without Love, Vocal (B or C) (Box 8, Folder 461)
  - A Million Dreams Ago, Vocal (F) (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - A Sinner Kissed an Angel (Box 24, Folder 2312)
  - A Swinging Ballad (Count Basie) (Box 10, Folder 623)
  - A Taste of Honey (Quincy Jones) (Box 18, Folder 1141)
  - A Tree in a Meadow, Vocal (Ab) (Box 20, Folder 2094)
  - A Wink and a Smile, Vocal (C) (Box 21, Folder 2107)
  - Ac-cen-tu-ate the Positive (Box 21, Folder 2011)
  - Accustomed to Her Face (Box 10, Folder 597)
  - Accustomed to Her Face (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 664)
  - Ace in the Hole, Vocal (Bb) (Box 11, Folder 674)
  - Across the Alley from the Alamo (Stan Kenton) (Box 11, Folder 666)
  - Adios (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - African Waltz (Oliver Nelson) (Box 13, Folder 811)
  - After Supper (Count Basie) (Box 24, Folder 2345)
  - After the Lovin', Vocal (A) (Box 9, Folder 535)
  - After You've Blown (Box 9, Folder 535)
  - After You've Gone (Roy Eldridge) (Gene Krupa) (Box 16, Folder 1015)
  - Afterglow (Woody Herman) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ain't that a Kick in the Head (Dean Martin), Vocal (Eb) (Box 20, Folder 2095)
  - Ain't Misbehaven, Vocal (G) (Box 16, Folder 1134)
  - Ain't Misbehaving, Vocal (Ab) (Box 24, Folder 2320)
  - Ain't She Sweet (Les Elgart) (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Ain't She Sweet (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 28, Folder 2552)
  - Airegin (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Airport (Les Brown) (Box 19, Folder 2034)
  - Al-de-la, Vocal (F minor) (Box 23, Folder 2243)
  - Alexander's Rag Time Band (Box 15, Folder 958)
  - Alice Blue Gown (Glenn Miller) (Box 18, Folder 1165)
  - All about Love (Steve Lawrence), Vocal (B) (Box 21, Folder 2115)
  - All I Ask of You (Phantom of the Opera), Vocal (Bb) (Box 4, Folder 237)
  - All I Need is the Girl, Vocal (F) (Box 29, Folder 2598)
  - All of Me (Billy May) (Box 6, Folder 370)
  - All of Me, Vocal (C) (Box 7, Folder 427)
  - All of Me (Count Basie) (Box 14, Folder 892)
  - All of You (Count Basie) (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - All or Nothing at All (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (C) (Box 20, Folder 2081)
  - All the Cats Join In (Benny Goodman) (Box 29, Folder 3308)
  - All the Things You Are (Stan Kenton) (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - All the Things You Are (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - All the Things You Are, Vocal (F) (Box 9, Folder 533)
  - All Through the Day (Les Brown) (Box 9, Folder 537)
  - All the Way (Lou Rawls), Vocal (D) (Box 21, Folder 2129)
  - Alley Cat-Line Dance (Box 5, Folder 266)
  - Almost Like Being in Love, Vocal (Eb) (Box 16, Folder 1018)
  - Along the Santa Fe Trail (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Eb) (Box 11, Folder 704)
  - Alright, Okay, You Win (Count Basie) (Box 18, Folder 1111)
  - Alright, Okay, You Win (Joe Williams), Vocal (Box 23, Folder 2231)
  - Alright, Okay, You Win (Ralph Marterie) (Box 5, Folder 293)
  - Alright, Okay, You Win, Vocal (F) (Box 10, Folder 628)
  - Always (Billy May) (Box 8, Folder 448)
  - Always (Box 25, Folder 2403)
  - Am I Blue (Les Elgart) (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Am I Blue (Linda Ronstadt), Vocal (Box 20, Folder 2079)
  - Amanda (Duke Parsons) (Box 16, Folder 987)
  - Amapola, Vocal (Ab) (Box 11, Folder 715)
  - America (Box 14, Folder 843)
  - American Patrol (Glenn Miller) (Box 9, Folder 516)
  - Amore, Vocal (Ab) (Box 22, Folder 2190)
  - Amore (Box 22, Folder 2203)
  - And Her Tears Flowed Like Wine (Stan Kenton) (Box 12, Folder 755)
  - And I Love Her (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 28, Folder 2587)
  - And the Angels Sing (Benny Goodman) (Box 9, Folder 518)
  - And We Listened (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 24, Folder 2284)
  - Anema e Core, Vocal (Bb) (Box 22, Folder 2226)
  - Anema e Core, Vocal (Eb) (Box 26, Folder 2422)
  - Angel Eyes, Vocal (A minor) (Box 25, Folder 2374)
  - Annie Laurie (Ray Anthony) (Box 15, Folder 957)
  - Anniversary Song (Box 19, Folder 1184)
  - Another Day Another Dawn (Ray Anthony) (Box 21, Folder 2146)
  - Another Star (Box 5, Folder 277)
  - Anvil Chorus (Glenn Miller) (Box 17, Folder 1066)
  - Anything Goes (Al Cohn) (Box 16, Folder 992)
  - Anything Goes (Ted Heath) (Box 27, Folder 2494)
  - Apple Valley (Les Brown) (Box 15, Folder 924)
  - Apple Honey (Woody Herman) (Box 9, Folder 545)
  - April in Paris (Count Basie) (Box 9, Folder 579)
  - April in Paris (Glenn Miller) (Box 11, Folder 658)
  - April Showers (Woody Herman) (Box 12, Folder 749)
  - Arrivederci Roma, Vocal (Eb) (Box 20, Folder 2056)
  - Arrivederci Roma, Vocal (Eb) (Box 26, Folder 2459)
  - Artificial Flowers, Vocal (Box 29, Folder 3321)
  - Artistry in Percussion (Duke Ellington) (Box 28, Folder 2593)
  - Artistry in Rhythm (Stan Kenton) (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Artistry Jumps (Stan Kenton) (Box 14, Folder 853)
  - As Long as I'm Singing (Bobby Darin), Vocal (Bb) (Box 21, Folder 2150)
  - As Time Goes By (Ralph Marterie) (Box 11, Folder 661)
  - As Time Goes By, Vocal (G) (Box 15, Folder 936)
  - As Time Goes By, Vocal (Eb) or Solo (Box 20, Folder 2076)
  - At Last (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Box 4, Folder 199)
  - At Long Last Love, Vocal (Bb) (Box 12, Folder 733)
  - At Long Last Love (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 27, Folder 2508)
  - At Sundown (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Auld Lang Syne (Box 28, Folder 2544)
  - Auld Lang Syne (Box 23, Folder 2236)
  - Arthur Murray, Vocal (G) (Box 29, Folder 3319)
  - Autumn in New York (Stan Kenton) (Box 6, Folder 343)
  - Autumn in New York (Ralph Marterie) (Box 14, Folder 850)
  - Autumn in New York (Ray Anthony), Vocal (G) (Box 19, Folder 2018)
  - Autumn in New York, Vocal (C) (Box 21, Folder 2119)
  - Autumn Leaves (Ted Heath) (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Autumn Leaves (Ray Anthony) (Box 9, Folder 576)
  - Autumn Serenade Pastel (Harry James) (Box 9, Folder 572)
  - Avalon (Box 26, Folder 2414)
  - Azure (Billy May) (Box 18, Folder 1199)
  - Baby It's Cold Outside, Vocal (Db) (Box 25, Folder 2379)
  - Baby It's Cold Outside (Box 29, Folder 3311)
  - Bachanal (Billy May) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Back Bay Shuffle (Artie Shaw) (Box 16, Folder 978)
  - Back Home in Indiana, Vocal (C) (Box 12, Folder 750)
  - Back in Your Own Backyard (Les Brown) (Box 12, Folder 754)
  - Back to the Apple (Count Basie) (Box 21, Folder 2051)
  - Backbeat Boogie (Harry James) (Box 11, Folder 713)
  - Blacksmith Blues, Vocal (Bb) (Box 28, Folder 2590)
  - Bad Bad Leroy Brown, Vocal (G) (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Bad Bad Leroy Brown (Box 10, Folder 646)
  - Bag-a-Bones (Count Basie) (Box 18, Folder 1152)
  - Baia (Ralph Marterie) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bali Hai (Les Brown) (Box 7, Folder 402)
  - Bandstand Boogie (Les Elgart) (Box 8, Folder 460)
  - Bandstand Matinee (Ray Anthony) (Box 24, Folder 2318)
  - Baptism (Duke Parsons) (Box 16, Folder 988)
  - Bare Necessities (Harry Connick) (Box 28, Folder 2560)
  - Basically the Blues (Buddy Rich) (Box 15, Folder 935)
  - Basie Thing (Count Basie) (Box 24, Folder 2327)
  - Baubles, Bangles, and Beads (Ted Heath) (Box 13, Folder 835)
  - Baubles, Bangles, and Beads (Box 21, Folder 2127)
  - Baubles, Bangles, and Beads (Box 10, Folder 609)
  - Bei Mir Bist du Schon, Vocal (D) (Box 21, Folder 2116)
  - Beautiful Baby, Vocal (Ab) (Box 28, Folder 2588)
  - Beat Me Daddy, Eight to the Bar, Vocal (Bb) (Box 6, Folder 337)
  - Beautiful Ohio (Glenn Miller) (Box 5, Folder 303)
  - Beautiful Ohio (Ted Heath) (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Beautiful Baby, Vocal (Bb) (Box 28, Folder 2578)
  - Bedouin (Duke Pearson) (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Beer Barrel Polka (Box 20, Folder 2048)
  - Begin the Beguine (Artie Shaw) (Box 5, Folder 264)
  - Begin the Beguine (Ted Heath) (Box 12, Folder 775)
  - Begin the Beguine (Stan Kenton) (Box 14, Folder 852)
  - Begin the Beguine (Les Elgart) (Box 18, Folder 1157)
  - Begin the Beguine, Vocal (C) (Box 24, Folder 2287)
  - Beginning to See the Light (Harry James) (Box 14, Folder 854)
  - Beginning to See the Light (Les Brown) (Box 6, Folder 352)
  - Beginning to See the Light (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 28, Folder 2556)
  - Berkley Square (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Eb) (Box 10, Folder 625)
  - Berkley Square (Bobby Darin), Vocal (Box 24, Folder 2308)
  - Bernie's Tune (Count Basie) (Box 8, Folder 485)
  - Besame Mucho, Vocal (D minor) (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Beyond the Sea (Bobby Dain) (Box 19, Folder 2006)
  - Beyond the Sea (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 29, Folder 2611)
  - Bidin' My Time (Les Elgart) (Box 16, Folder 1001)
  - Big Mamma Cass (Buddy Rich) (Box 24, Folder 2334)
  - Big Sur Echo (Woody Herman) (Box 26, Folder 2440)
  - Big Sur Echo (Woody Herman) (Box 28, Folder 2555)
  - Big Swing Face (Buddy Rich) (Box 8, Folder 510)
  - Bijou (Woody Herman) (Box 18, Folder 1109)
  - Bill (Ted Heath) (Box 12, Folder 731)
  - Bill Baily, Vocal (C) (Box 7, Folder 389)
  - Birth of the Blues (Ray Anthony) (Box 10, Folder 629)
  - Birth of the Blues, Vocal (Eb) (Box 25, Folder 2346)
  - Birth of the Blues (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (G) (Box 25, Folder 2388)
  - Bittersweet (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 15, Folder 933)
  - Bizet has His Day (Les Brown) (Box 7, Folder 392)
  - Blue and Sentimental (Count Basie) (Box 5, Folder 310)
  - Blue Bayou (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Blue Bayou, Vocal (Bb) (Box 29, Folder 3317)
  - Blue Champagne, Vocal (Db) (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Blue Heaven (Ted Heath) (Box 19, Folder 1197)
  - Blue Monk (Woody Herman) (Box 28, Folder 2567)
  - Blue Moon (Les Brown) (Box 5, Folder 278)
  - Blue Moon (Ray Anthony) (Box 19, Folder 1193)
  - Blue Moon, Vocal (Db) (Box 25, Folder 2393)
  - Blue Moon (Marion Evans) (Box 26, Folder 2446)
  - Blue Moon (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Db) (Box 28, Folder 2572)
  - Blue Prelude (Box 7, Folder 435)
  - Blue Rain (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Blue Room (Box 13, Folder 809)
  - Blue Skies (Box 5, Folder 281)
  - Blue Skies (Bobby Darin) (Box 25, Folder 2352)
  - Blue Skies (Tommy Dorsey), Vocal (F) (Box 4, Folder 207)
  - Blue Tango (Box 7, Folder 409)
  - Blues for Kapp (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 19, Folder 1178)
  - Blues in Hoss Flat (Count Basie) (Box 18, Folder 1129)
  - Blues in the Night, Vocal (F) (Box 18, Folder 1110)
  - Bluesette (Les Brown) (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Body and Soul (Stan Kenton) (Box 5, Folder 290)
  - Body and Soul, Vocal (Db) (Box 19, Folder 1180)
  - Body and Soul (Box 23, Folder 2035)
  - Body and Soul (Box 21, Folder 2128)
  - Body and Soul (Colman) (Box 21, Folder 2112)
  - Bon Voyage (Les Brown) (Box 16, Folder 990)
  - Boo Hoo (Guy Lombardo) (Box 7, Folder 441)
  - Boogie Blues (Gene Krupa) (Box 6, Folder 367)
  - Boogie Woogie (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 4, Folder 247)
  - Boogie Woogie Bugle Boy (Andrews Sisters), Vocal (Box 17, Folder 1078)
  - Boomerang (Buddy Rich) (Box 27, Folder 2513)
  - Boulevard of Broken Dreams (Ralph Marterie) (Box 8, Folder 504)
  - Boy Meets Horn (Duke Ellington) (Box 11, Folder 676)
  - Braniff Time (Count Basie) (Box 25, Folder 2349)
  - Brazil Samba (Box 11, Folder 707)
  - Bridge Over Troubled Waters (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 13, Folder 812)
  - Broadway (Count Basie) (Box 4, Folder 224)
  - Brooklyn Boogie (Louie Prima) (Box 5, Folder 282)
  - Brotherly Shove (Box 21, Folder 2130)
  - Brown in Fourths (Les Brown) (Box 13, Folder 818)
  - Bubbles (Count Basie) (Box 24, Folder 2292)
  - Bugle Call Rag (Glenn Miller) (Box 10, Folder 642)
  - Bunny Hop (Ray Anthony) (Box 13, Folder 782)
  - But Beautiful (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - But Beautiful (Stan Kenton) (Box 21, Folder 2135)
  - But Beautiful (Stan Kenton) (Box 14, Folder 868)
  - But Not for Me (Les Brown) (Box 10, Folder 605)
  - But Not for Me, Vocal (Bb) (Box 17, Folder 1024)
  - Bye, Bye Blackbird, Vocal (F) (Box 18, Folder 1125)
  - Bye, Bye Blackbird, Vocal (F) (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Bye, Bye Blackbird (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 665)
  - C Jam Blues (Count Basie) (Box 14, Folder 846)
  - C Jam Blues (Box 17, Folder 1043)
  - Cab Driver (Ted Heath) (Box 4, Folder 212)
  - Cabaret (Ted Heath) (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Cabaret, Vocal (Ab) (Box 24, Folder 2329)
  - Cachita (Box 22, Folder 2198)
  - Cajun Walk (Buddy Rich) (Box 27, Folder 2525)
  - Call Me Irresponsible (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Camel Hop (Woody Herman) (Box 28, Folder 2573)
  - Camelot (Les Brown) (Box 16, Folder 1021)
  - Camptown Races (Ray Anthony) (Box 11, Folder 709)
  - Can't Get Used to Loosing You (Andy Williams), Vocal (C) (Box 22, Folder 2179)
  - Can't Take That Away from Me, Vocal (Eb) (Box 8, Folder 451)
  - Canadian Sunset (Box 13, Folder 776)
  - Canadian Sunset (Doc Severson) (Box 14, Folder 874)
  - Can't Help Lovin' That Man, Vocal (G) (Box 28, Folder 2526)
  - Captain Ahab (Woody Herman) (Box 26, Folder 2458)
  - Caravan (Box 14, Folder 905)
  - Caravan (Box 19, Folder 1185)
  - Careless, Vocal (F) (Box 4, Folder 240)
  - Caribbean Clipper (Glenn Miller) (Box 4, Folder 229)
  - Carico (Artie Shaw) (Box 6, Folder 359)
  - Carmellos by the Freeway (Bob Florence) (Box 17, Folder 1071)
  - Carolina in the Morning (Woody Herman), Vocal (Box 16, Folder 1128)
  - Catty Corner (Woody Herman) (Box 26, Folder 2456)
  - Celebration (Buddy Rich) (Box 13, Folder 819)
  - Celery Stalks at Midnight (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Celestial Blues (Woody Herman) (Box 13, Folder 837)
  - Challenger (Ray Anthony) (Box 28, Folder 2576)
  - Changing Partners, Vocal (C) (Box 24, Folder 2309)
  - Changing Partners (Patty Page), Vocal (Box 24, Folder 2304)
  - Channel One Suit (Buddy Rich) (Box 13, Folder 802)
  - Charade (Quincy Jones) (Box 24, Folder 2299)
  - Charade (Bobby Darin), Vocal (F) (Box 26, Folder 2432)
  - Charleston Alley (Charlie Barnet) (Box 25, Folder 2401)
  - Charleston (Box 5, Folder 250)
  - Charmaine (Ted Heath) (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - Charmaine (Billy May) (Box 13, Folder 815)
  - Chase It Brother (Count Basie) (Box 11, Folder 702)
  - Chasers (Break Time), Vocal Group (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chattanooga Choo Choo (The Modernaires) (Glenn Miller), Vocal Group (Box 10, Folder 640)
  - Chattanooga Choo Choo (Box 5, Folder 279)
  - Cheek to Cheek (Harry James) (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - Cheek to Cheek (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 21, Folder 2021)
  - Cheek to Cheek (Billy May) (Box 21, Folder 2125)
  - Cheerful Little Earful (Count Basie) (Box 8, Folder 495)
  - Cheers (Box 29, Folder 3331)
  - Chelsea Bridge (Duke Ellington) (Box 14, Folder 841)
  - Cherokee (Charlie Barnet) (Box 4, Folder 205)
  - Cherry (Box 7, Folder 398)
  - Cherry (Harry James) (Box 22, Folder 2192)
  - Cherry Pink (Box 7, Folder 436)
  - Cherry Pink (Box 22, Folder 2216)
  - Cherry Point (Count Basie) (Box 24, Folder 2298)
  - Chicago (Eydie Gormé), Vocal (Eb) (Box 5, Folder 257)
  - Chicago (Buddy Rich) (Box 17, Folder 1042)
  - Chicago (Modernaires) (Tommy Dorsey), Vocal Group (Bb) (Box 11, Folder 656)
  - Chloe (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 9, Folder 582)
  - Choo Choo Boogie, Vocal (F) (Box 23, Folder 2266)
  - Chop Sticks (Ray Anthony) (Box 14, Folder 897)
  - Christopher Columbus (Ray Anthony) (Box 7, Folder 440)
  - Cecilia (Les Brown) (Box 12, Folder 764)
  - Ciribiribin (Harry James) (Box 4, Folder 200)
  - Clarinade (Benny Goodman) (Box 6, Folder 360)
  - Clarinet Polka (Box 23, Folder 2269)
  - Clementine (Bobby Darin), Vocal (Box 22, Folder 2178)
  - Close to You (The Modernaires) (Glenn Miller), Vocal Group (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Close to Your Eyes (Box 20, Folder 2085)
  - Cocktail Hour (Box 17, Folder 1056)
  - Coffee Song (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Coffee Song (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Box 26, Folder 2437)
  - Coffee Time (Les Brown) (Box 8, Folder 491)
  - Colonel Bogey Meringue (Count Basie) (Box 16, Folder 976)
  - Come Dance with Me (Count Basie) (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 19, Folder 2020)
  - Come Fly with Me (Count Basie), Vocal (F) (Box 21, Folder 2120)
  - Come Fly with Me (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 28, Folder 2538)
  - Come Rain or Come Shine (Woody Herman) (Box 10, Folder 651)
  - Come Rain or Come Shine, Vocal (F) (Box 16, Folder 1023)
  - Come Rain or Come Shine, Vocal (Bb) (Box 28, Folder 2562)
  - Come Rain or Come Shine, Vocal (B to C) (Box 29, Folder 2600)
  - Come Rain or Come Shine (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 25, Folder 2387)
  - Concerto for Clarinet (Artie Shaw) (Box 28, Folder 2582)
  - Contrast (Jimmy Dorsey) (Box 9, Folder 519)
  - Cooks Tour (Ray Anthony) (Box 13, Folder 783)
  - Copacabana (Box 5, Folder 276)
  - Copacabana, Vocal (Bb) (Box 29, Folder 3320)
  - Cornball (Tutti Camarata) (Box 28, Folder 2540)
  - Corner Pocket (Les Brown) (Box 8, Folder 493)
  - Corner Pocket (Count Basie) (Box 12, Folder 727)
  - Cotton Pickin' (Harry James) (Box 5, Folder 271)
  - Cotton Tail (Duke Ellington) (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - Cotton Tail (Buddy Rich) (Box 15, Folder 932)
  - Could I Have This Dance (Ann Murral), Vocal (C) (Box 23, Folder 2268)
  - Count Down (Bill Potts) (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Country Road (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 13, Folder 836)
  - Craziest Dream, Vocal (Ab) (Box 5, Folder 297)
  - Craziest Dream, Vocal (C) (Box 27, Folder 2470)
  - Crazy (Patsy Cline), Vocal (Box 20, Folder 2078)
  - Crazy Rhythm (Woody Herman) (Box 14, Folder 891)
  - Crazy Rhythm (Woody Herman) (Box 16, Folder 1008)
  - Cream in my Coffee (Les Brown) (Box 6, Folder 320)
  - Crescendo in Blue (Duke Ellington) (Box 27, Folder 2530)
  - Critics' Choice (Buddy Rich) (Box 16, Folder 995)
  - Crush on You, Vocal (F) (Box 23, Folder 2249)
  - Crush on You, Vocal (Db) (Box 29, Folder 2615)
  - Cry Me a River (Box 13, Folder 801)
  - Cry Me a River, Vocal (Bb) (Box 21, Folder 2101)
  - Cuban Pete (Box 20, Folder 2041)
  - Cuddle Up a Little Closer (Les Elgart) (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - Cute (Count Basie) (Box 15, Folder 933)
  - Dance Ballerina (Box 17, Folder 1055)
  - Dancing in the Dark (Billy May) (Box 8, Folder 469)
  - Dancing in the Dark (Ray Anthony) (Box 19, Folder 1196)
  - Dancing in the Dark (Artie Shaw) (Box 21, Folder 2156)
  - Dancing in the Dark (Jerry Mulligan) (Box 24, Folder 2339)
  - Dancing in the Dark (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 25, Folder 2386)
  - Dancing in the Street (Box 16, Folder 979)
  - Dancing on the Ceiling (Ralph Marterie) (Box 6, Folder 321)
  - Dancing on the Ceiling (Ray Anthony) (Box 13, Folder 824)
  - Dancing on the Ceiling (Les Brown) (Box 26, Folder 2425)
  - Danke Schoen (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Danny Boy (Glenn Miller) (Box 6, Folder 348)
  - Danny Boy (Box 22, Folder 2196)
  - Darktown Strutters' Ball, Vocal (Box 29, Folder 3314)
  - Darn That Dream (Box 9, Folder 526)
  - Darn That Dream (Bill Holman) (Box 15, Folder 916)
  - Day by Day (Box 10, Folder 598)
  - Day by Day, Vocal (F) (Box 23, Folder 2250)
  - Day by Day, Vocal (C) (Box 25, Folder 2390)
  - Day In Day Out (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 26, Folder 2417)
  - Days of Wine and Roses, Vocal (F) (Box 10, Folder 601)
  - Days of Wine and Roses (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 24, Folder 2285)
  - Dead Man's Blues (Billy Potts) (Box 12, Folder 732)
  - Dear Heart, Vocal (F) (Box 29, Folder 2618)
  - Deed I Do (Count Basie) (Box 10, Folder 617)
  - Deep Night (Ray Anthony) (Box 17, Folder 1194)
  - Deep Purple (Woody Herman) (Box 18, Folder 1153)
  - Deep River (Ray Anthony) (Box 15, Folder 956)
  - Desafinado (Box 15, Folder 915)
  - Desafinado (Count Basie) (Box 18, Folder 1140)
  - Diane (Billy May) (Box 11, Folder 669)
  - Diggin' for Dex (Count Basie) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Diminuendo in Blue (Duke Ellington) (Box 27, Folder 2535)
  - Dinah (Ralph Marterie) (Box 11, Folder 675)
  - Dinah (Woody Herman) (Box 18, Folder 1127)
  - Disk Jockey Jump (Gene Krupa) (Box 9, Folder 588)
  - Dizzy Fingers (Benny Goodman) (Box 29, Folder 3309)
  - Do You Ever Think of Me (Les Elgart) (Box 12, Folder 724)
  - Does Your Heart Beat for Me (Russ Morgan) (Box 11, Folder 660)
  - Domino (Buddy Rich) (Box 17, Folder 1084)
  - Don'cha Go Away Mad (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 26, Folder 2412)
  - Don't Be That Way (Benny Goodman) (Box 5, Folder 261)
  - Don't Be That Way (Benny Goodman) (Box 7, Folder 424)
  - Don't Be That Way (Les Elgart) (Box 18, Folder 1148)
  - Don't Blame Me (Box 11, Folder 708)
  - Don't Blame Me (Billy May) (Box 14, Folder 858)
  - Don't Get Around Much Anymore (Bill Holman) (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Don't Get Around Much Anymore, Vocal (Box 4, Folder 223)
  - Don't Get Around Much Anymore (Box 15, Folder 920)
  - Don't Get Around Much Anymore (Natalie Cole), Vocal (Box 20, Folder 2087)
  - Don't Get Around Much Anymore (Duke Ellington) (Box 24, Folder 2342)
  - Don't Sit Under the Apple Tree (Glenn Miller), Vocal (D) (Box 12, Folder 772)
  - Don't Worry About Me, Vocal (Eb) (Box 21, Folder 2124)
  - Donkey Serenade (Artie Shaw) (Box 20, Folder 2038)
  - Down for Double (Count Basie) (Box 9, Folder 525)
  - Down South Camp Meeting (Box 28, Folder 2585)
  - Dr. Wong's Bag (Woody Herman) (Box 26, Folder 2439)
  - Dr. Wong's Bag (Woody Herman) (Box 27, Folder 2517)
  - Dragnet (Ray Anthony) (Box 13, Folder 785)
  - Dream (The Modernaires), Vocal Group (Box 12, Folder 760)
  - Dream (Ray Anthony), Vocal Group (Box 20, Folder 2098)
  - Dream (Box 13, Folder 793)
  - Dream Dancing (Ray Anthony), Vocal Group (Box 18, Folder 1136)
  - Dream the Rest (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Dreamers Holiday (Glenn Miller) (Box 13, Folder 784)
  - Dreamsville (Box 6, Folder 383)
  - Dreamsville (Henry Mancini) (Box 23, Folder 2232)
  - Drippin' Honey (Duke Parsons) (Box 10, Folder 637)
  - Drum Boogie (Gene Krupa) (Box 6, Folder 368)